Chopped a glass and hit the tile, well not proud, now you're on trial.
Painful and sick and to make the best, an hour later still in distress.
Ironing a wrinkled set of teeth, now the crease is mine to keep.
Spilled the paint, missed the time, flips the capsule and stabbed the guy.
It's always harder to fix than it was to break, well don't move it's ten hours late.
Stabbed your fingers, oops you flew it.
Now you've stopped with booing with everyone, screw it twice, well for the cost of bad advice.
Take one line, crash the site, get Baudel through half the night.
Throw the tag off, no return, now your wallet gets to burn.
Cut the wire you should've cut, full house smells like a rut.
You bleeped once and nuked a vibe, now you owe beers to the whole tribe.
It's always R.M.Fix, then it was too late, the signal slipped, now you're on all day eggs.
Snap the scissors and fight for joys.
Hope you like patching, metaphorical, all is at once.
Wrecking fast, good luck cleaning up your past.
It's always harder to fix.
Too much to break and break from the icing on your tongue.
But stand it slow, break it quick, rougher than a human strip.
That's hurt twice, but ends rich.
Cut it wrong, and now it's flesh.
One slit, ten steps back.
That's universal, one glob back.